Oh... Excuse me, getting off!
I'd like to get—
Go ahead.
Oh... Thank you.
Hey, don't you think that guy looks so cool?
I know, right?!
My heart fluttered just now!
Such a beautiful face!
Wanna go ask him for his number?
You think I should?
Huh?
Is that a...
Skirt?
Y-Yoi Takiguchi-sama!
Please accept this!
Um... I'm sorry, but with this sort
of thing... I'm not really...
What's this?
Again with the gifts?
Nobara, Kotobuki.
Even in high school, you've still got it.
You failed to say no again, huh, Yoi-chan?
Well, I feel bad...
A tall, slender physique.
Or maybe you're actually enjoying it, huh?
A slightly low-pitched voice.
That's not...
A masculine face inherited from my parents.
You're super popular with the girls.
I wish someone would give me presents, too.
Yoi Takiguchi.
First year in high school.
Oh, stop that.
I'm a girl.
Right, right... Come on, let's head to class.
But everyone calls me...
Hey, Prince.
Isn't that the Prince?
You mean the first-year?
Hey, you're right.
Hey, Prince!
I kinda get it.
Yoi-chan is way more appealing
than most of the guys around here!
That's right, it was during
last year's field day...
A girl fell down, and Yoi-chan carried
her all the way to the finish line!
And came in first place.
Oh, man, she was so cool!
How should I put it? Yoi-chan is like the
hero from a shojo manga, y'know?
A hero, huh?
I wonder when the Prince will come.
Oh man, your face is so red!
What, seriously?
Oh, speak of the devil.
Sorry, I'm going to take a detour.
'Kay.
Um...
Here. You dropped this.
Oh, thank you so much!
People do seem to take me more for a
hero or a prince than a princess.
Well, it can't be helped, looking like I do.
Ow...
Oh, my bad.
I didn't see you there.
You all right?
What...
What's with this guy?
You know...
You're really beautiful.
Huh?
You're a dude?
Get out of the way.
Feels like I'd remember that guy...
Fourth period is study hall
Textbook P30-46 Report
Must be submitted!
The Prince is lost in thought.
Huh? Something wrong, Yoi-chan?
So beautiful...
You look pissed.
Not really.
What? No way!
Asking me if I'm a dude right to my face...
Ichimura-senpai and the others are
going to play soccer in the gym!
Talk about rude!
Yay! We get to watch them! Lucky us!
What's all the fuss?
Oh, it must be about the other "Prince."
"Other Prince"?
Yep. Rumor has it that his
dad is a multi-millionaire
and is already in charge
of two or three companies.
Also, the number of women he's brought to
tears is easily in the triple digits.
Doesn't sound that credible,
even for a rumor.
Ichimura-senpai!
A prince, huh?
Well, not my concern.
Oh?
Senpai!
Do your best at PE!
He's the one from this morning!
He's the one from this morning.
Yo.
Your ass okay?
What? Yoi-chan? What?
What do you mean ass?
Oh...
Prince...
What?! You know Ichimura-senpai?!
From where?! How?!
Hey, huh? Um.
When did you guys meet?!
Hang on...
Are they saying he's the "Prince"?!
Hey, you know Yoi Takiguichi?
Huh?
Well, not really.
What? Someone famous or something?
Totally famous.
What, you don't know?
Isn't she the one they call
"Prince" even though she's a girl?
Huh?!
He's not some super beautiful dude?
He's a girl?!
Yeah, she's a girl.
Come on, that's just
straight-up rude, man.
Seriously?
I don't usually talk to others in class,
so that took me by surprise.
I'm glad I was able to clear up
any misunderstandings, but...
Oh, I see. You guys just
bumped into each other, then.
I'm so glad.
We'd lose both our princes
if the two of them got together!
The hell was that about?
I see I'm no longer considered a girl
even by the girls in my own class.
I'll just eat some choco
anpan and forget about it...
Hey there, miss.
What time d'you clock out?
Hey, don't ignore me.
Excuse me.
Huh?
Don't you see that you're bothering her?
If you keep this up, I'm
going to call the police.
Huh? Who the hell're you?!
You should mind your own business!
Hey—
Whoa.
Huh?
Nice cheesy line.
Th-Th-The provisional Prince?!
Huh? Done already?
Welp, I guess it's all right.
It's more than enough to
go viral on the Internet.
"Drunk gets called out for harassing
a woman and goes apeshit."
Ya little punk!
Hey! Delete that right now!
What a pain.
Huh?! Ya—
I'm saying, "Beat it, you're annoying."
Read the room, yeah?
This guy...
He's more like a hoodlum than a prince...
Oh, hey. What are the odds?
We keep bumping into each other, huh?
What?
You live around here? Lit.
He didn't know it was...
Why ya little...
Don't ya ignore me!
It's cowardly to attack
someone from behind!
Hey! What are you guys doing out here?!
Huh? Um, well, this is...
Manager, that guy is the one to blame.
I-I didn't do nothin'.
This way.
Huh, um...!
You've got some nerve causing
trouble in my store!
Ow! Ow!
Quiet! You should be ashamed of yourself!
That's our manager!
Man, that was a close one.
How did I end up in this situation?
Anyway, that move was amazing.
That thing you did like this!
Did you study that stuff?
A little karate.
Karate! That's so cool!
Man, I kinda understand
how those girls feel now.
Y'know, back there...
you really did look like a prince.
Well...
I'm not a prince
because I want to be one.
I consider myself to be
perfectly normal,
but everywhere I go,
it's "Prince" this and "hero" that.
I'm always put on some pedestal.
Why am I...
telling him all this?
So what?
What if you are a prince?
Not all girls need to be demure, y'know?
It's all right if there's a prince-like
girl in the mix once in a while.
Actually, that "thing" you just did...
It made my heart flutter.
A lot.
Th-Thank you very much...
Conscientious, are ya?
Man, you're great, Yoi-chan.
So intriguing.
He used "-chan" for me...
And how does he even know my name?
I mean, you're this beautiful and you've
never been treated like a princess before?
Wh-What? N-No, never...
The guys around you must
have horrible taste in women.
Calling me beautiful...
I can't tell if this guy is messing
with me or being serious...
Ya want me to carry you like a princess?
What?
All right. Hold here and wrap
your hands around my neck.
What?!
And, up.
What do you think you're doing?!
Huh? I'm carrying you like a princess.
No, that's not what I mean!
Put me down!
You'll end up with a broken arm!
Nah, this won't break my arms.
Th-That's not what I meant!
Whatcha think?
Feeling pretty heroine-like, right?
This is wrong.
Just kiddin'.
But it is a pretty cheesy thing to say...
Um...
It's time for me to go home!
This is wrong.
I'm not the one who gets swept off my feet
if I fall down on field day.
I'm not the one who gives
chocolate on Valentine's day.
A tall, slender physique.
A slightly low-pitched voice.
A masculine face inherited from my parents.
I know better than anyone that
I'm not fit to be a heroine.
That's why...
I shouldn't get my hopes up.
I'll be okay.
I was just surprised, that's all.
That's the first time something
like that has ever happened to me.
So... just calm down!
What the...
Man, that was real nice.
After sleeping on it,
I've started to feel super embarrassed
about what happened yesterday.
I'm going home!
Wha, why?
Whaaa
Ugh! I'm being way too self-conscious!
I've never shown that side
of myself to anyone before!
Oh. Hey, it's Yoi-chan.
What happened yesterday?
You surprised me
when you just up and left.
I-I'm sorry, something urgent came up.
Right.
I'm gonna go on ahead.
Sorry, my bad.
Are you sure you want
to be seen talking to me,
considering everyone calls you a prince?
People might take it the wrong way.
That's fine by me.
Let them take it the wrong way.
Actually, y'know...
I'm interested in you, Yoi-chan.
Huh?
Is this some sort of prank or something?
You know, where someone is hiding
and filming us or something...
No, no way!
Do I look like someone who would—
You do.
You say that, but if you don't get what
I mean when I say, "I'm interested,"
I don't know how else to put it...
It's a little different from "love"...
Man, it's hard putting it into words...
Oh, I got it!
It's more like, "I want to watch
you forever!"
Huh?
Y'know, like how you just want to keep
looking at something that's beautiful?
Like I don't want to take my eyes
off ya for even a split second.
That kind of thing?
You know...
That's exactly something
a stalker would say...
Come on, a stalker wouldn't come up and
tell their victim about it.
So, to start,
how 'bout we have
lunch together today, Yoi-san?
No...
No, I'm good!
Really, I haven't had much of
a relationship with men my whole life...
Yoi Takiguchi?
Nope, there's no way.
She's more handsome than me!
Girls are better when they're
cute, don't ya think?
Isn't that the Prince?
Prince!
So cool!
So...
So...!
What is up with this guy?!
I can't believe he calls me like that.
Yoi-chan's looking kinda sexy today.
He should really call me Takiguchi-san...
Even her melancholy face is picturesque.
And "I want to watch you forever,"
like I'm some sort of house plant...
I can't imagine someone called "Prince"
would ever bother to take interest in me.
You know... You're really beautiful.
That's right.
I bet he says that
sort of thing to all the girls.
Yoi-chan.
Let's eat lunch!
Oh, okay.
Is your bento box today
your dad's specialty dish?
Must be nice.
I've got to try it again sometime.
Sure, stop by anytime.
Oh, there she is.
Yoi-chan, you got some time right now?
Th-The provisional Prince?!
I can't believe he actually came!
Huh? Huh?! Did he just say "Yoi-chan?"
Are those two really in
that sort of relationship?!
Not good!
S-Senpai!
There's a committee meeting
this afternoon, isn't there?
Huh? Uh, what?
Then we can't be standing here!
Now, let's go!
Hey.
Just come on. Come on.
Huh, you're real strong.
Is this karate, too?
Huh? So, what exactly was
the deal with those two?
Even your sudden lies are
flawlessly proper, aren't they?
Better question... What is this place?
The old school building.
I come here all the time with my buds.
Not that. I mean, why do I have to
eat lunch in a place like this?!
Well, 'cause you don't want
others to see you, right?
Ugh, whatever. I'll just
eat quickly and head back...
Thank you for the meal.
Um, aren't you going to sit?
Don't mind if I do.
Right there?!
Or would it be more strange
to eat sitting far apart?
Or...
Was he doing that
to be considerate?
I'm just overthinking it.
He has such long, beautiful fingers.
I wonder if that's what it means
to have a well-balanced face?
Is that why he's called the Prince?
Oh, never mind.
I'd better just get through my meal.
Huh? Curry?
Shoot... I just did it without thinking...
Not only that, isn't it
really elaborately prepped?
We...
We run a curry restaurant, so...
Seriously?!
Wow, a curry restaurant!
I've never met someone who runs one!
I get that a lot.
Whoa, for real? That's amazing!
You get to eat delicious
curry whenever you want!
Honestly, I don't really
want the word to get out.
People would give me
weird nicknames...
Weird nicknames?
You swear you won't laugh?
I swear.
The...
C-Curry Prince...
Curry Prince
See? I told you!
I don't like saying it.
I like that you run a curry place.
It's cute.
Huh?!
How is that cute?!
Please don't patronize me...
I'm not patronizing you.
The way you act so
self-conscious about it...
How unexpected it is...
You're just cute, Yoi-chan.
There he goes again.
Could you please stop teasing me like that?
I never know how to respond.
Yep, and it's great.
I don't know what it is...
but there's something
about you, Yoi-chan,
that keeps me at the edge
of my seat, wanting more.
What kind of face are you gonna make next?
Show me more.
This is the first time in my life
that I'm getting hit on by a guy.
This guy...
I can't even!
And that guy is the Prince.
Prince and Prince
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Yukari Murase-Louden
Andy Ellis
Gabriella Alabanza
Salem Alabanza
Elizabeth Ellis